[Music]
we've been looking at the etf business
for quite a long time but we wanted to
make sure that the our offering was
differentiated and actually added to our
value proposition in everything we do we
want to make sure that we bring to
Canadians financial solutions that allow
them to achieve their goals and we
believe that bringing ETFs to the
marketplace and partnership with
dimensional fund advisers allow us to
offer a great value proposition
we believe that there's a huge
opportunity for growth in ETFs in Canada
AUM are going to keep growing Canadians
consumers financial advisors want to add
ETFs to their portfolio so it's the
right solution at the right time we may
see a slowdown in the velocity of the
new issuers coming to the marketplace
but we believe that in terms of assets
it's going to keep growing and we're
just at the beginning
dimensional fund advisers is one of the
largest asset managers in North America
they've got about six hundred fifty
billion dollars assets under management
and they've grown that over the past
thirty five years they have a singular
focus on multi factor factor based
investing and that's what they do across
all of their business they believe very
strongly that there's information in
prices and they use that to manage their
portfolio over the past thirty five
years they've worked really hard on the
implementation side of investing which
is important in strategies like
multi-factor
yet there's four factors that
dimensional views as having risen to the
level of a dimension as we know there's
hundreds of factors out there but before
that dimensional have identified as
having the highest probability of
increasing expected returns our market
so fixed income versus equity size
company size relative value and
profitability
the Phoenix says was the first market
that listed ETF and actually has a long
history in developing index based funds
I think their commitment to the market
and their help with new issuers and
their brand in the marketplace is very
strong
[Music]